Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Building Drawings and Large-Format Materials OS
New York University Archives
- Series VII: List of Collections for Separated Materials
  - Records of the RISM Cross-Cultural Comparisons of Aging and Longevity Study (The Longevity Study) (RISM RG 15) (Flat-file-folder 5)
    These oversized materials are part of the Records of the RISM Cross-Cultural Comparisons of Aging and Longevity Study, RISM RG 15.
  - Alumni Groups, School of Medicine and Law School Records (RG 40.23, 40.22, and 40.1): Annual dinner-related, 1892-1912, 1921-1922 (Box Shared University Archives 132, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Charles Edwards Papers (MC 97) (Box Shared University Archives 132)
  - Sergio A Korff Papers (MC 110), October 17, 1940 (Box Shared University Archives 132)
  - Oscar Falnes Papers (MC 135): Diplomas and World War I certificate, 1911, 1916, 1918, 1933 (Box Shared University Archives 132)
    This oversized material is part of the Oscar Falnes Papers (MC 135) and was removed from Box 17. It consists of two diplomas and one item entitled "Roll of Honor, World's Great War for Democracy."
  - Alice Keliher (MS 139): diploma and certificate, 1930, 1945 (Box Shared University Archives 132)
  - S.R. Slavson Papers (MC 141): 9 Certificates, 1945-1975 (Box Shared University Archives 132)
  - Michael Fennell (MC 142): Diplomas, 1965, 1967 (Box Shared University Archives 132)
  - Nicholas Wahl Papers (MC 146): Charles De Gaulle posters, etc., 1953-1958, 1968 (Box Shared University Archives 132, Flat-file-folder 6)
  - Records of the French-American Foundation (MC 147) (Box Shared University Archives 132)
    This oversized material is part of the Records of the French-American Foundation (MC 147).
  - Richard Courant Papers (MC 150) (Flat-file 6, Drawer 7)
  - John Brademas Congressional Papers (MC 168): portrait in wood pieces, campaign and lecture posters, etc. (4 folders), circa 1959-1981 (Box Shared University Archives 132, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 5)
    These oversized materials are part of the John Brademas Congressional Papers, MC 168.
  - Lawrence J. Majewski Papers (MC 171) (Box Shared University Archives 145, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Map of "The Synagogue January 1969"
    - Miscellaneous Drawings
    - Miscellaneous Tracings
  - Jill Claster Papers (MC 252): photograph of Washington Square Park graduation ceremony and group photograph, 1986, undated (Flat-file-folder 1 Left)
  - Flora Kaplan Papers (MC 300): Thomas Jekyll Exhibition Brochure (Flat-file 2, Drawer 19)
    This brochure is part of the Flora Kaplan Papers, MC 300.
  - J.E. Sexton: Certificate to practice law in New York State, 1931 (Box Shared University Archives 132)
  - Henry Clay Edwards: Letter, painting of woman, sketches of dresses, 1890, not dated (Box 12)
  - Henry Mitchel MacCracken Administrative Records: University Heights campus maps, diagrams, property sketches, 1893-1896 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Charles Butler papers: maps, 1846-1864, undated (Flat-file-folder 8)
- Series VIII: Posters and Event Fliers
  - Original art/graphics for NYU Magazine articles, school logos/shields, graphics of university buildings, campus maps, event posters, portraits of staff, NYC skyline, 1989-2002 (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Exhibition poster re: NYU and Anti-Vietnam, by graduate assistant of Dept of History and University Archives, undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 11)
    Original Location: "1968 Revisited" Exhibition (MC 132)
  - Presentations, movie screenings, musical events, etc., 1988-2001 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Sports events, lectures, music, some posters signed by performer, etc. (3 folders), circa 1980s-1990s (Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Organizational charts for NYU in general, School of Engineering, University Development, and School of Education departments, 1920-1930 (Box 18)
  - Silver Jubilee party for fraternities; Strike Coordinating Committee; anti-Vietnam; Sesquicentennial Celebration; Emily Warren Roebling dedication; etc., 1932, 1969-1983 (Box 18)
  - Humanities Council events/seminar posters, 1973-1986 (Box 18)
  - Humanities Council posters for various events, 1973-1990 (Box 18)
  - Humanities Council posters for various events: seminars, etc., 1979-2000 (Box 18)
  - 91st Washington Square Outdoor Art Exhibit, 1977 (Box Shared University Archives 127)
  - Posters and Event Fliers (Box 3)
  - Posters and Event Fliers (Box 4)
  - Posters and Event Fliers (Box 5)
  - Glee Club poster and event announcements, 1958, 1961, 1963 (Box 18)
  - Citizen Involvement in Urban Affairs HUD/NYU Summer Study poster, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Music concerts, comedy shows, movie screenings, NYU anniversary, etc. Some posters signed by performers, circa 1980s-1990s (Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Reproductions of NYU buildings, landmarks, and events. Also, posters for concerts, shows, movies, and lectures (3 folders), circa 1980s-1990s (Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Library-related poster, certificates of honor for NYU libraries, 1985-1990 (Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Concerts, movie screenings, Women's History month, anniversary events, lectures, etc., 1970s-1990s (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Educational and Cultural Alliance, 1977-83, undated (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Concert posters: NYU Choral Arts Society and Glee Club, 1975, undated (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Protest Vietnam sign, advertising posters for NYU sports, events, 1970s-1990s (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Bobcat (Library Catalog) Poster, circa 1980s (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Institute for Afro-American Affairs (later Institute of African American Affairs) Event Poster, circa 1970s (Flat-file-folder 5 Left)